brainjar.com 2017-12-28

# BrainJar.com: Experiments in Web Programming

## Privacy Policy

This policy applies to the BrainJar.com web site.

### Personal Information

Any personally identifiable information you voluntarily provide (such as your name and email address when sending comments or questions) will be held in the strictest confidence. It will not be sold or otherwise provided to other parties.

### Log Files

Information collected in [web server logs](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Server_log) (IP address, internet service provider, user agent, requested page, date and time, etc.) is used for generating aggregate reports on web site traffic. These logs do not contain personally identifiable information.

### Cookies/Web Bugs

This site uses temporary [cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie), where needed, for storing individual [session information](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Session_management). They may also be used for illustrative purposes in programming examples. These are not shared with third parties.

Advertisements on the site are provided via Google AdSense.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

For more information, please see Google's [advertising privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

### Links to Other Sites

This policy applies only to the BrainJar.com web site. Any web site linked to from this site will be covered under its own privacy policy.
